

ABOUT ME

Successful at delivering excellent quality work before deadlines during my professional and academic experience. Now, a proficient web developer, pragmatic and diligent.

Excited to learn new technologies, striving to write clean and scalable code using best practices. Efficient and resourceful in achieving my objectives, in bringing code to life in amazing designs.

WEBSITES & SOCIAL LINKS

Portfolio:

https://luchianemil.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/EmilLM

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/emilluchian-990/

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

JAPANESE

SPANISH

EMIL LUCHIAN

Full stack (MERN) web developer



+40741125806

✓ luchianemil@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

SELF-STUDY

Bucharest Nov 2019 - present

Full stack web developer

Continuously self-improving by learning new technologies and practices.

Learned: Node, Express, MongoDB and more. **Portfolio: luchianemil.com**

CODER'S LAB

Bucharest Sep 2019 - Nov 2019

Graduate

Graduated from an intensive course to become a front-end developer. The course emphasized rigorous exercises and exams.

DIGITAL WEB PROPERTIES

Bucharest Aug 2016 - Jun 2017

Editor

My main activity consisted in writing articles on a variety of subjects regarding technology, politics, science and nature for various companies interested in being listed on Google News.

POLITICALL

Bucharest Nov 2013 - Mar 2015

Editor

A Romanian independent publication where I was responsible for writing articles on current international events and analyze social-political developments.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF BUCHAREST

Bucharest 2015

Master's Degree

Degree in political science: international relations.

UNIVERSITY OF BUCHAREST

Bucharest 2013

Bachelor's Degree

Degree in European studies from the Faculty of Philosophy.

SKILLS

Main stack: MongoDB - Express - React - Node

UI/UX: Html5, Css3/Scss, Bootstrap, Photoshop, Adobe XD

Front-end: Javascript ES6+, React, Next.js, Material-UI, SWR, jQuery, Vue

Back-end: MongoDB, Node, Express, Firebase, Mongoose

Tools/Misc: Git/Github, npm, Rest Api, MVC, CMS, SSR/CSR

Learning: GraphQL/Apollo, Typescript, SQL, React Spring, React Native

Intern

INTERNSHIPS

FOREIGN INTELLIGENCE SERVICE

Bucharest Jul 2014 - Aug 2014

My activity consisted in the gathering and analysis of information from open sources regarding international events as well as writing briefings, essays and various types of activities similar to those of an intelligence analyst.

HOBBIES

EXERCISE, SPORTS, GAMING, POLITICS, READING